<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sections on Always Open 7-11</title>
    <link>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sections on Always Open 7-11</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/coding/</guid>
      <description>Methodology   Create a R Shiny application that allow us to view the location of 7-11 and its relations with other amenities.
  To perform spatial point pattern analysis on 7-11 in Taiwan
  Choropleth Map to visualize the population in Taiwan
  Kernel Density Estimation of 7-11 and other amenities in Taiwan
  Auto-correlation with 7-11 stores and various amenities
  Second Order Analysis such G-function and L-function</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/conclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/conclusion/</guid>
      <description>Scope of Work Project Timeline Data Sources    Name Sources     7-11 &amp;amp; Family Mart Convenience stores https://www.319papago.idv.tw/lifeinfo/7-11/7-11-00.html   Population Density https://gis.ris.gov.tw/dashboard.html?key=B07   Other Taiwan open source data https://data.gov.tw/    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>Challenges and Mitigation As 7-11 store location is not readily available in geospatial data format in their website. It is required to scrape data from 7-11 website and perform geocoding to get the latitude and longitude for the 7-Eleven location.
Taiwan uses a different coordinate system as Singapore, and they have multiple projection system throughout the country. However, we will be only be using epsg:3828 where the bounding box cover the mainland of Taiwan without the islands surrounding it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/images/</guid>
      <description>Storyboard </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>Application System Architecture </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/project/</guid>
      <description>Literature Review In literature review, we have done our topic on the following area to enhance our preliminary knowledge:
Plotting a colored Taiwan Map based on population: This is a simple project where the author analyzes Taiwan population distribution on a choropleth map. There are many insights we gain from this project such as how we should process the data. For example, not all files have an English version, this project show how we can join the data even if they are in different languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alwaysopen7-11.netlify.app/post/about/</guid>
      <description>Project Motivation Convenience stores are a huge deal in Taiwan. Especially the Japanese-American chain, 7-Eleven is ubiquitous in Taiwan with 5,000 over stores distributed around the country. It provides various services that help people with their daily activities such as bill payment, cash withdrawal, top-up, delivery and pickup parcels. With that, the 7-11 in Taiwan plays an important part in peoples’ daily lives. It has also been integrated in peoples’ modern part of life by delivering brilliance service with every visit unlike the 7-11 in Singapore where people visit only when there is no other alternative.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
